QUOC TRUNG CHU

FULL STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

◆ DRESDEN, GERMANY

• DETAILS •

Dresden Germany tru.chu.qu@gmail.com

Date / Place of birth 11.10.1998 Hanoi, Vietnam

> Nationality German

LINKS

LinkedIn

Github

Personal Portfolio Website

SKILLS

Java

Python

HTML & CSS

React

JavaScript

SQL

Docker

Git

LANGUAGES

English

German

Spanish

Vietnamese

PROFILE

Full stack software engineer who was been collecting hands on experience in personal projects, as well as in different jobs throughout the whole time at the university. Furthermore interested in machine learning and data science. For further details on my personal projects, feel free to visit my Github or my personal portfolio website.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Full Stack Software Engineer at Conimon GmbH, Dresden

November 2020 — Present

Development of Java-based web applications that enable automatic and cloud-based machine diagnostics. Implemented crucial parts in the frontend as well as in the backend.

Working with technologies like Spring, Vaadin, Postgres, Docker and more

Student Assistent at NeuroImaging Center TU Dresden

April 2019 — October 2020

Development of a web application based on Python with the aim to simplify the operation of image processing processes in the field of brain research.

Working with technologies like Bottle, Postgres, Docker and more

Student Assistant at Media Center TU Dresden

October 2018 — March 2019

Software development for the website of the TU Dresden based on Python and an in-house framework built on top of Plone. First experience in a professional environment.

EDUCATION

Master of Science, Technische Universität Dresden

April 2021 — Present

Currently studying Computer Science at the TU Dresden with focus on artificial intelligence, data science and software technologies

Bachelor of Science, Technische Universität Dresden, Dresden

October 2017 — April 2021

Bachelor thesis with the topic 'Generating Taxonomy from large text corpora using Machine Learning'

Graduated with a final grade of 2.2

Abitur, Martin Andersen Nexö Gymnasium, Dresden

August 2009 — July 2017

Math and science specialized school with advanced courses in Math, English and Physics.

Graduated with a final grade of 1.6